# JingLiang Jiang

Love nature, snow and freedom. Never give up and never stop to seek new chanlege. Hope to experience all different kinds of life.

godvmxi@gmail.com | +86-18017302045 | GitHub | Twitter | Capability |

### About Me

Full Name Jingliang Jiang

Experience 9 years total, 6 years in multi-national companys, including AMD and Cisco, Good

at programing and IT maintain.

Degree Master's and Bechelor's Degree for EE, full-time for Bechelor and part-time for

Master

Available September

# **Technology Stack**

Network-Be familiar with most of Cisco router and switch configure and troubleshooting and

ing understand the the internal design logic, excented at vlan, voip, AP

Service: Be familiar with seting up all kinds of network service, NTP, DHCP, DNS, OPEN-

STACK, Windows Server AD, Mail System, Office 365, Backup System

System Linux, Windows, Mac

Virtualiza-Exsi, PVE

tion

IT Hare-Evalute, Purchase, Configure, Assembly all kinds of related IT equipment.

ware IT Technol-

ogy

Server HW/SW customized, workstation HW/SW customized, operating system customized, software customized, Printer, Networking and related IT equipment.

Video Codec Have a full understanding about the video codecs, both in asic design and software

stack develop

C/C++, Python, C#, Bash Language

# Working Experience

2017/12-Now Advanced Micro Devices, Inc Senior Firmware Engineer

> AMD today develops high-performance computing and visualization products to solve some of the world's toughest and most interesting challenges.

- Making test platform purchase plan to support the diag team for asic verification and bringup, including networking device, workstation platform and so on.
- Setting up all necessary hardware platform to support team work.
- Developing the video codec (H264,HEVC,VP9) IP verification framework during both for the pre-silicon and post-silicon period.

2014/5-2017/11 Shanghai InfoTM Microelectronics Co., Ltd. Senior Software Engineer; IT team leader

InfoTM Co., Ltd. is an intelligent system operator with integrated circuit design and development as the core and provides intelligent terminal by integration and optimization of supply chain and offers system service supported by big data operating.

- Make IT equipment plan, and lead the IT team to maintain the IT equipment.
- Make the bringup plan for ASIC design team.
- Handle the video codec IP verification.
- Handle the misc IP verification.
- Implement new software video stack for video application
- Support customer for new software stack

#### 2011/10-2014/04Cisco Systems, Inc. Software Engineer

Cisco is the worldwide leader in IT, networking, and cybersecurity solutions.

- Develop Virtualization thin client
- Implement Networking Protocal
- Develop virtualization software client in thin client
- Add misc device support for thin client, such as printer, IR remote controler, touching screen, XBox kinect and so on.
- Add vehicle can bus device support for thin client.

# Education

2012/9–2015/6 Master's Degree in Electronic Information Engineering, Chinese Academy of Sciences University (part-time)

2007/9–2011/6 Bachelor's Degree in Electronic Information Engineering, Qingdao University

# Projects

#### 2019/6-Now

Mi100/200 AI GPU verification - AMD Senior Firmware Engineer

AMD GPU AI solution for facebook and other customers

- Setup all kinds of server and PC platforms to verify the GPU card
- Help Board Enginer team to debug hardware issues ,incude pci-e, memory, power
- Add necessarg cases to verify all features for video codec IP in asic.
- Dig with design and other teams to solve related video issues

#### 2017/12-2019/8 Oberon/Ariel AGPU verification - AMD Senior Firmware Engineer

AMD AGPU game station solution for Sony PS5 and later game station

- Setup all kinds of server and PC platforms to verify the GPU card
- Help Board Enginer team to debug hardware issues ,incude pci-e, memory, power
- Add necessarg cases to verify all features for video codec IP in asic.
- Dig with design and other teams to solve related video issues

#### 2018/9-2019/9 Arden AGPU verification - AMD Senior Firmware Engineer

AMD AGPU game station solution for MicroSoft XBOX and later game station

- Setup all kinds of server and PC platforms to verify the GPU card
- Help Board Enginer team to debug hardware issues ,incude pci-e, memory, power
- Add necessarg cases to verify all features for video codec IP in asic.
- Dig with design and other teams to solve related video issues

### 2018/9-2019/9 OpenStack Deploy - INFOTM Senior Software Engineer

Use OpenStack to re-orgnize the structure of the company.

- Design server and networking structure and define the budget.
- Use openldp as a global use authority method
- Merge all development tools to openstack

#### 2014/6-2017/9 Asic Chip verification - INFOTM Senior Software Engineer

Inform provided various chips for IPC, Game Station, SportDV, Android Pad, such as Imapx 200/800(pad), Apollo 1/2/x(IPC,SportDV,NVR), Corona 2/3(Game Station for Tencent), I handled the vodeo codec IP verification, including in pre-silicon, post-silicon, driver implement, video framework implement.

- Keep video codec IPs(From Synopsys, include H1,H2,G1,G2) match the criterion of the design plan
- Help design team to estimate and measure the efficiency and power consumption
- Implement the BMS code based uboot to verify the design in RTL, FPGA and bringup period
- Verify other misc IPs in some projects(RS232, SPI, Flash Controler, OSD and so on)

### 2016/9-2017/9 Asic Chip software stack update - INFOTM Senior Software Engineer

Update the whole software stack for new framework to support more flexible video application.

- Design the video flow framework and implement the main base job
- Implement most of video modules for new video framework
- Implement supporting modules for new framework(such video filesystem(parse and store bitstream based ffmpeg), rtp tools, video quality setting tools and so on )
- Implement new build system for new software stack, based on buildroot and gemu.

## 2017/3-2017/11 Customer Support - INFOTM Senior Product Support Engineer

With the chip and software stack update, I switch my work to focus on the support for customers.

- Help customers to solve issues during the whole application
- Help customer's hardware/software teams to dig root cause of bug, then solve by myself or assign the solution to correct team
- Track project process

#### 2011/10-2014/4 Bluebird thin Client - Cisco Software Engineer

Build thin client for Virtulization system.

- Add networking support for thin client (Wlan Client, Multi-AP, Manage VLAN, TR069, VPN Client)
- Implement management Restapi, web ui and framework modules for aboving modules
- Add CAN-Bus support, including software moduleis, hardware modules and muli-vehicles
- Track the hardware design from Foxconn

#### 2011/10-2012/2 Bluebird vehicle client module - Cisco Software Engineer, Hardware Engineer

A car client module for vehicles, can support the thin client usage and server usage

- Add CAN-Bus module to collect the statistics of the vehicles
- Add GPRS/3G moudles to support communication between client and server

- $\bullet\,$  Add Bluetooth moudles to support communication among client, mobile, thin client
- Track and double check the HW design of Foxconn